[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a malapropism?", "correct_answer": "He is at the pineapple of his career.", "incorrect_answers": ["Round and round the ragged rock the ragged rascal ran.", "Water, water everywhere, nor any drop to drink.", "Able was I ere I saw Elba."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country does the typical breakfast consist of Caff\u00e8 e latte and a pastry?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cambodia", "Scotland", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the instant messaging system (or IM), what do the letters SYS mean?", "correct_answer": "see you soon", "incorrect_answers": ["seeing your sister", "system is down", "still your spouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the mascot of the University of California at Irvine?", "correct_answer": "Anteater", "incorrect_answers": ["Maverick", "Gaucho", "Banana Slug"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which plant with tasty fruits is also a wireless handheld device?", "correct_answer": "Blackberry", "incorrect_answers": ["Strawberry", "Blueberry", "Gooseberry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When he was a baby, action star Jackie Chan was nicknamed Pao Pao. What does this literally mean in Chinese?", "correct_answer": "Cannonball", "incorrect_answers": ["Bang-bang", "Extremely fast", "Loud cry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie won the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 81st Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Slumdog Millionaire", "incorrect_answers": ["Milk", "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button", "The Reader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Spanish word for dog is pero.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Beavers are the second largest rodents in the world after which animal?", "correct_answer": "Capybara", "incorrect_answers": ["Muskrat", "Mountain Marmot", "Sea Otter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Luxembourg, which is a member of NATO, contribute to NATO?", "correct_answer": "by maintaining a small army", "incorrect_answers": ["by maintaining the sixth largest NATO air force", "by allowing extensive US and British military installations on its territory", "by financially supporting a navy even though is has no coastline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are most foxes generally classified according to their diet?", "correct_answer": "Omnivores", "incorrect_answers": ["Specialized eaters", "Insectivores", "Carnivores"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By what name was the closest planet to the Sun called by the Greeks?", "correct_answer": "Hermes", "incorrect_answers": ["Kokhav Hamah", "Hermaon", "Mercury"]}]